<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>resources on Deeper Breaths</title>
    <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/categories/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in resources on Deeper Breaths</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://deeperbreaths.org/categories/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Airway Clearance Therapy</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/treatments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/treatments/</guid>
      <description>Airway Clearance Therapy www.smartvest.com
IPV - Intrapulmonary Percussive Ventilation delivers small bursts of air through a mouthpiece into lungs, vibrates chest, loosens mucus deep in airways. Www. verywellhealth.com
OHFO - Oral High Frequency Oscillation low volume, high frequency jet oscillation to lungs through a mouthpiece. Uses sound frequency, helps clear carbon dioxide and sputum. Same website
PEP - Positive Epiratory Pressure use facemask or mouthpiece while inhaling and exhaling as normal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From our kids to your kids</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/from-our-kids-to-your-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/from-our-kids-to-your-kids/</guid>
      <description>From our kids to your kids Favorite things to do during vests: Prodigy math game, little legos &amp;ndash; especially new sets, Art for kids hub on youtube, Em Winn on Amazon Prime Video, Curiosity Streams, playing with siblings with toys, parents reading books (Who is/What was series is educational and great for kids 2nd - 6th or beyond), coloring books, color by number. Khan Academy kids. Of course apps are always a hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/learning/</guid>
      <description>Learning websites for medical information:  pcdfoundation cff copd foundation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/motivational/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/motivational/</guid>
      <description>Motivational/inspirational: www.runningonair.net Mary is an inspiring PCD warrior, living life at full saturation!
Child-authored book, PCD Has Nothing on Me. by Chloe Ferndandez
Search on instagram or facebook, hashtags
 #airwayclearancetherapy #primaryciliarydyskinesia #pcd #cysticfibrosis  Cystic Fibrosis has far more resources surrounding aiway clearance and hospitalization support, as it is more well-known, researched, and public. Primary Ciliary Dyskinesia is still in the newer stages of diagnosis and research, but every moment that passes, more learning is happening!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up for success</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/setting-up-for-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/setting-up-for-success/</guid>
      <description>Setting up for success Have something that only gets done during treatments. Rotate a few things often. Get a good organization system. Make it a convenient location. Ideas for cabinets that fit vests and medication. If the sky&#39;s the limit, do a custom built-in. Make the space cozy. Good lighting. Sensory Table with understorage &amp;ndash; ikea table with orbeez or water beads in it. Something contained but fun. Little legos inside those bins with a surface to build on would be excellent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand Washing</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/hand-washing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/hand-washing/</guid>
      <description>hand washing </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>