<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deeper Breaths</title>
    <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Deeper Breaths</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:06:28 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://deeperbreaths.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>form letters</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/printables/form-letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:06:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/printables/form-letters/</guid>
      <description>form letters   school form letter for Primary Ciliary Dyskinesia
  school form letter for Cystic Fibrosis
  school form letter for Lung Health
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:06:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is primary ciliary dyskinesia? Primary Ciliary Dyskinesia is an inherited disorder that affects cilia. Cilia are tiny, hair-like structures in various places in the body, including the airways, sinuses, and ear canals. The structures form incorrectly, causing difficulties in clearing mucus. There may also be differences in the organ placement in the abdomen, with some or all organs reversed. Some have heart defects, and some have no spleen or multiple spleens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shop</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:06:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/shop/</guid>
      <description>Storefront </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From our kids to your kids</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/from-our-kids-to-your-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/from-our-kids-to-your-kids/</guid>
      <description>From our kids to your kids Kids like variety! We like to do a few different things during our vest treatments to keep us occupied, and we like to switch things up so that it stays fun and doesn’t feel like a chore! We broke the activities up into categories, and our mom and dad will include links to buy them if those are available.
Sensory:   Homemade slime! We love to make slime and then play with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cough spot coloring page</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/printables/cough-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/printables/cough-spot/</guid>
      <description>Cough Spot Coloring Page This will be a pdf printable showing kids how to safely cover their cough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>medication schedule</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/printables/medication-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 21:06:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/printables/medication-schedule/</guid>
      <description>medication schedule </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/motivational/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/motivational/</guid>
      <description>Motivational/inspirational: www.runningonair.net Mary is an inspiring PCD warrior, living life at full saturation!
Child-authored book, PCD Has Nothing on Me. by Chloe Ferndandez
Search on instagram or facebook, hashtags
 #airwayclearancetherapy #primaryciliarydyskinesia #pcd #cysticfibrosis  Cystic Fibrosis has far more resources surrounding aiway clearance and hospitalization support, as it is more well-known, researched, and public. Primary Ciliary Dyskinesia is still in the newer stages of diagnosis and research, but every moment that passes, more learning is happening!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/about/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/about/about-us/</guid>
      <description>About Us Hello! We are Karen and Steve, parents of soon-to-be six kids, two of whom are diagnosed with Primary Ciliary Dyskinesia. We will see about the sixth after he is born! We have been navigating the space and lifestyle of airway clearance treatments for almost six years now, and thought that we could share some things we have learned along the way. Stop in, explore, and learn how to live a full life by taking deeper breaths!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up for success</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/setting-up-for-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/setting-up-for-success/</guid>
      <description>Setting up for success Have something that only gets done during treatments. Rotate a few things often. Get a good organization system. Make it a convenient location. Ideas for cabinets that fit vests and medication. If the sky&#39;s the limit, do a custom built-in. Make the space cozy. Good lighting. Sensory Table with understorage &amp;ndash; ikea table with orbeez or water beads in it. Something contained but fun. Little legos inside those bins with a surface to build on would be excellent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>