<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on Deeper Breaths</title>
    <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on Deeper Breaths</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up for success</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/setting-up-for-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/setting-up-for-success/</guid>
      <description>Setting up for success Tip #1: Keep activities fresh. Have something that only gets done during treatments, and rotate a few things often.
 Check out our From our kids to your kids page for ideas that would work for you!  Tip #2: Organize the chaos. Get a good organization system, in a convenient location.
 I hope to add a few cabinets that would work to fit the vests without modifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From our kids to your kids</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/from-our-kids-to-your-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/from-our-kids-to-your-kids/</guid>
      <description>From our kids to your kids Kids like variety! We like to do a few different things during our vest treatments to keep us occupied, and we like to switch things up so that it stays fun and doesn’t feel like a chore! We broke the activities up into categories, and our mom and dad will include links to buy them if those are available.
Sensory:   Homemade slime! We love to make slime and then play with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/motivational/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/motivational/</guid>
      <description>Motivational/inspirational: www.runningonair.net Mary is an inspiring PCD warrior, living life at full saturation!
Child-authored book, PCD Has Nothing on Me. by Chloe Ferndandez
Search on instagram or facebook, hashtags
 #airwayclearancetherapy #primaryciliarydyskinesia #pcd #cysticfibrosis  Cystic Fibrosis has far more resources surrounding aiway clearance and hospitalization support, as it is more well-known, researched, and public. Primary Ciliary Dyskinesia is still in the newer stages of diagnosis and research, but every moment that passes, more learning is happening!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airway Clearance Therapy</title>
      <link>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/treatments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeperbreaths.org/resources/treatments/</guid>
      <description>Airway Clearance Therapy We hope this page would be a resource for parents to understand the different types of machines available. We were only told of one device when we initially got our diagnoses, so as the years have progressed we have learned about other machines, other treatment options, travel-friendly options, and have wanted to explore deeper so we could choose the best for our family. Hopefully this page can be an easy-to-understand resource for you, so you can be fully informed before getting locked into one device and company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>